What?
Hold on, wait.
Boss,
what do you mean,
warm up?
Ted, I did my research.
You used to be a star.
If it weren't for
that accident,
you'd be in the Hall of Fame by now.
I need you to warm up.
Ted?
Ted Vincent?
The same guy the media used to call
the best player in NCAA?
No way! You're
my head coach?
Grace.
I'm the head coach.
I can't just go out there and be a player.
Actually, you can.
I registered you as a player before we started.
You're officially
on the roster.
Go on and warm up.
My legs healed...
but I haven't played
in so long.
Can I really do this?
Hey!
You want that Super Bowl ring or not?
Huh?
You got this.
Now,
I'll take the championship that belongs to me.
Maybe...
Maybe this is
my last shot to
step on that field
as a player.
The past injuries are behind me.
They won't stop me now!
Alright.
Let's crush them.
Yeah!
Yes!